=================================================================
Better Bodies 2.0 Falconer Leather
                  	By: Korana 
=================================================================

1. Installation
2. Description/Use
3. Credits
4. Contact and Usage

=================================================================
1. INSTALLATION
=================================================================

To install the plugin, unzip the .rar file into your Morrowind/Data 
Files directory.

=================================================================
2. DESCRIPTION/USE
=================================================================

This plugin adds several "Falconer Leather" items, for both male
and female characters. The articles of clothing/armor are designed
for use with Better Bodies 2.0. 

Included are clothing AND armor versions of:

-Male and Female pants
-Female lace front pants
-Female bodice with bracers
-Male lace up shirt
-Female fold top, high heeled leather boots
-Male ranger boots
-An open sided leather skirt
-Leather coats for both male and female

I have also included a quiver and a sheild.

The armor and clothing peices are interchangable to make different
outfits.  Please be advised that the coat may clip with the skirt 
on the edges in certain positions.  The quivers may also clip with
items or with the character.  The meshes were not designed with the
other in mind. I apologize for the clipping with those two items.

The clothing, armor, and equipment can be bought from a female high
elf in the lower section of the Balmora Fighter's Guild.  She sells
both the armor and the clothing, they are distinguishable by their
names.

SCREENSHOTS INCLUDED

=================================================================
3. CREDITS 
=================================================================

~NoLiv for the female bodysuit mesh, the female skirt mesh, the 
 female tights mesh, and the female boots mesh   

~Joel Braddock (a.k.a. Mantodea) for the coat meshes 

~Junkmail for the male boots mesh

~Dongle for the quivers and sheild

~Derreko for the male vest mesh

~Silaria & Neuman for the pants mesh and base texture (It was too
good...I just gave it a bit more leather texture). I would also like
to thank Silaria for the hair I used for the merchant.

~Gorg for the merchant's ear texture.

~Rhedd for the head mesh I used for the merchant's face.

=================================================================
4. Contact & Usage
=================================================================

Feel free to use these items as you like!  Please give credit to the
above makers for their meshes however.  I would enjoy a mention in the
readme, or maybe even an email, but it's not required!

IF you would like to contact me, please feel free.  I can be reached at:

roxykittyd@adelphia.net


Distribution- Feel free to distribute this where you like, and how you like.
AS LONG AS IT IS NOT OUTSIDE THE ELDERSCROLLS SERIES.  Thanks!