=================================================================
Better Bodies 2.0 Peasant Gowns
                  	By: Korana 
=================================================================

1. Installation
2. Description/Use
3. Credits
4. Contact and Usage

=================================================================
1. INSTALLATION
=================================================================

To install the plugin, unzip the .rar file into your Morrowind/Data 
Files directory.

=================================================================
2. DESCRIPTION/USE
=================================================================

These "Peasant Gowns" are full gowns, designed for use with Better
Bodies 2.0.  The gowns have full sleeves, full skirts, and bodices
that tie up with a bow.

The included esp file adds a small shop to Pelagiad, located just inside
the castle's walls.  The shop sells all of the peasant gowns, some
expensive clothing from the original game, and also two pairs of
Better Bodies boots made to go with the gowns.

A larger article of clothing might bring up some issues of clipping: 
There is slight clipping in the arm area at certain angles....but it is
very minimal. Depending on what else is worn with the gown you may 
experience slight clipping on the bottom of the back of the legs when
running.  (But I've yet to have it when not wearing anything under the gown.) 
The hands are slightly in the fabric of the skirt.  It's much less apparent
in game that it is in the cs.


=================================================================
3. CREDITS 
=================================================================

~Robearberbil for the Gown meshes...and for putting up with my ideas,
 and sometimes even making them come to life!    

~NoLiv for the boots mesh

~Neuman for the dress pattern from "Neuman's Black Leather II"

~Calislahn and Regan for the following equipment: scissors, pin
 cushion, and measuring tape.

~Better Bodies for the body model used for the mannequin (which will 
 NOT equip clothing intentionally). 

~Rhedd for the head mesh I used for the merchant's face and the 
 mannequin's head. 

~Gorg for the merchant's hair mesh and ear texture.

=================================================================
4. Contact & Usage
=================================================================

Please do NOT use the sewing equipment without obtaining permissions
from either Calislahn or Regan.

Also, please give credit to any of the above creditors for any of their
items you use in your own projects.

IF you would like to contact me, please feel free.  I can be reached at:

roxykittyd@adelphia.net


Distribution- Feel free to distribute this where you like.