                          *****Lady Death Companion V 2.0 BETA******
					      by Korana

1.  What is this?
2.  Installation
3.  Changing your prexisting character 
4.  Credits and Usage
5.  Contact

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
1.  What is this?
 

This plugin adds the companion Lady Death and a companion hell hound ...based off of 
Chaos Comic's character.

ALSO INCLUDED IS A PLAYABLE RACE VERSION OF LADY DEATH.  The body uses the seamless
version of Better Bodies 2.1.

Lady Death can be found in Hell's Lair.  To get there, check out the Therys Ancestrial 
tomb (near the Balmora egg mine) or the shrine of Ashalmawia.  Lady Death will also
transport you back to the lair if you choose to return.
 
Lady death comes with an outfit...warning, the cape is not physiqued and causes clipping
at times.  She also comes with a custom sword by Robearberbil.

Requires Morrowind, Bloodmoon, and Tribunal.  Cleaned with Tesame.

-Custom birthsign art for the playable race option
-The lair plays an mp3 when you enter. You can also choose to play it
 through a "musicians skull" in the lair
-Bookart added
-MAJOR companion changes (see below)

***BETA TESTER NOTES***

Please check and make sure that the functions/aspects listed below in the readme do indeed
work.  Also keep an eye out for anything I left out of the readme.  If you can test this
with other companions please check for dialogue conflicts.


**********************************COMPANION INFORMATION**************************************

Lady Death now has a hell hound that follows her orders.  The hell hound will not take
commands from you.  The hell hound can:

-regenerate his health slighty
-be healed by Lady Death
-water breate
-water walk
-levitate
-be sent home if you wish to no longer travel with him

*Travel:

-She can transport herself, the hell hound, and you to Hell's lair.
-She can transport herself and you to Mornhold, Royal Palace Reception room 
 (Fixed the travel placement so that you dont wind up on top of one another after teleportation)
-She can transport herself and you to Balmora mages guild
-She also has the option of returning home without you. The hell hound will go with her.
-The hell hound can't teleport with you to mornhold and the mage's guild. However, Lady Death 
 has the option of sending the hound home by itself at any time. 

*Stats/Skills:

Lady death will report her stats to you.

*Health:

-Lady death and the hound both have minor regenerative abilities. 
-Speak to Lady Death and she will tell you the health percentages of herself or the hound.
-Lady Death can be told to heal herself or the hell hound through dialogue.  No potions are 
 needed...She will cast a spell on herself or the hound.
-Both Lady Death and the hound have minor waterbreathing abilities to prolong their health while
 swimming.

Please note she will not heal the player.

*Spells:

You can inform Lady Death to:

-Levitate
-Waterwalk
-Dispel all Magic
-Summon A skeletal minion

Both her and the hound will not leviate or walterwalk for long if the player does not 
cast a similar spell.

She should cast leviate/waterwalk on herself and the hound if the player casts a similar spell
automatically.

Please note currently she does return to normal position after casting the minion spell until
its duration is up.  If this bothers you selecting the spell option again will cause her to
return to normal positon.

*Combat:

-I removed her ability to function with marksmen weapons. She is a very good fighter with her 
 custom sword however.
-Lady Death also summons a skeletal minion automatically when in a fight.
-Lady Death will also cast a fire damage spell while in combat.
-The option of telling her what type of combat to use has been removed. (was in version 1)

WARNING! The combination of her, the hell hound, and the minion can be a force to be reckoned
with. It is your choice if you wish to use her at lower levels.  Please do not blame me if you
find the game un-balanced.


*Following/Warping-

-The hell hound warps to Lady Death. Lady Death warps to you. The two of them follow quite well.
 However you CAN loose them if you activate a teleportation device before the companion gets a 
 chance to warp to you. Warping is disabled during combat and for a few seconds after...so 
 teleportation during or directly after combat will cause you to become seperated from the 
 companion.
-Just in case she happens to be in the wrong place, you can tell her to move aside. 
 She does...rather well.
-You can have her follow you, stay put, or wander around.


*Dialogue
There have also been some dialogue changes for atmosphere, functionality, and to cut down on
conflicts with other companion mods.

*Leveling

I believe I used Grumpy's leving script.  From his readme:

"This mod makes use of an auto-leveling system that I've used for some time.  
There is nothing in-game to tell you that the companion is leveling, but it works
 just the same.  Every time the player successfully rests, the leveling script runs 
and makes compairison checks against the player's stats to see if any changes have occured.  
If there have been changes, then adjustments are made.  Attributes are at or near 
those of the player's.  Both armors and weapons are changed according to the player's level."

Also, if the player somehow levels DOWN...the companion's skills will not lower.

*Other Features:

-Companion Share
-Auto Sneak....she will begin sneaking if the player does.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 

2.  Installation

 Extracting the files directly into your Morrowind directory should do the trick.
   But if not:
    
     - The meshes folder "KO" should be placed in your 
          "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Meshes" directory

     - The textures should be placed directly into your 
           "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Textures" directory

     -  The esps should be placed loosely in your
	   "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles" directory

     -  The icons folder "KO" should be placed in your
           "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Icons" directory
     
     -  The music file "physcoromance.mp3" should be placed loosely in your
           "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Music" directory
    
     -  The bookart file "KOLadydeaths.tga" should be placed in your
           "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Bookart" directory


     -  This read me you can do what you please with.  

Make sure you enable the mod in the Morrowind Launcher before playing.

!!!!DO NOT USE VERSION 1 AND VERSION 2 TOGETHER!!!!

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

3. Changing your prexisting character into Lady Death.

Yes it is possible.  Please note this may cause problems with your game...make sure you
backup your saves and SAVE YOUR GAME BEFORE YOU TRY THIS.

Open up the console by hitting the ~ key and type in "enableracemenu"
This will open up a menu to change your race, hair, face, etc. 
Changing your race can cause some temporary issues, however reloading most of the
time will solve them.

  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

4. Credits, Usage, and Thanks

~Robearberbil for creating the sword 

~Durgoth for the thigh high boots, top mesh, and slip mesh.

~Grumpy for the Companion v3 scripts

~Baratheon79 for the "Skaal Companion - Corana" scripts...and all the help and input
 that was given. I would have never been able to succesfully use the animal companion
 aspect without you!

~Slantize for the mp3 "physcoromance" and for being kind enough to release music for
 other people to use/distribute for non-profit activities.
 
~Better Bodies team for the meshes I used and base texture for the body and hands..
 and especially Erstam for creating the seamless version of the meshes.

~Rhedd for his head mesh

~Gorg for the hair mesh...which I increased the size on. And also the original basis
 for the cape....which I made double sided, and modifed for better bodies.  I also
 increased the size.

~wolvie615 for wanting this and helping me with the ideas

~and of course...Chaos Comics.



Feel free to use her as you like! Just give some credit please!  You may also use the
hair, outfit, beds, weapon, or creatures added to this plugin as well.
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

5. Contact

feel free to email me at:  Roxykittyd@adelphia.net 
                                     or
                           miss_bad_kitty_21@yahoo.com