************************************************************************
                            Provincial Bath Shoppe v.1
			           by Korana

************************************************************************
-----------
Description
-----------	

This mod adds all the items you can dream up to add to your Morrowind Bath rooms!  The shop is
located nestled up against a corner of the castle in Pelagiad.  The shop keeper will offer you
a catalog when you first speak with her, please look at the catalog to see how I have grouped some
of the items.  I tried to create Bath sets for you to decorate your Morrowind homes with!

The shop offers:

                           **All items have new meshes and textures.** 
                 **This is not a mod where stock potions got new names and effects.**          

-FURNITURE: Wallscreens, bath tubs, bath basins, and mirrors (3 types).  All furniture has placement   scripts.  You may rotate, and move them, as you please.  PLEASE NOTE: The white basin, rose basin,    and claw  foot tub will need water added them to in game.  They are seperate meshes.  The water    meshes are  available for sale, and are scripted for placement.  You can also bathe in the tubs!

-ART: paintings and tapestries. All art has placement scripts.  You may rotate, and move them, as you  please.

-Over 90 soaps!  Most are by me, and use photo textures of real soap or soap wrappers.  All soaps by   me are distinguishable by their large icons.  Please do not send me emails complaining about the    fact that the icons don't look like little bars of soaps.  If you had several hundred icons to make,  you wouldn't want to make little soaps either!  Several donated soaps have also been added (see    credits.)  They have their own icons.

-Animated perfumes and colognes.

-CLOTHING:  Wearable bath towels, and bath robes.  **These items are for Better Bodies**  Please       note, the robes with (M) next to the name are monogramed with gold deadric letters.  They say "me".
 Male and Female have different colors, however, the Monogramed robes do make a few of the male        colors available to females.  Please note, when you drop the bath robes you will have a colorful      package, much like how items are gift wrapped at expensive stores.

-Lotions, bath salts, powders,etc.  All of these have alchemical or ingrediant properties.

-Bath towels, washcloths, unfolded washcloths, and bath mats.  All available in several colors.
 They are also designed to match the wearable towels and robes.

-Loofahs!

-Brushes!

-Hand held mirrors!  Please note, the mirrors are textured on both sides.  They have been scripted so  that you can flip them over and view both sides.  When you first drop the mirror, the mirrored side   will show.  When you activate the mirror the second time, it will flip over and show the design       side.  The third time you activate the mirror, it will go back into your inventory.

-Silver shave mortar and pestle, to go with the male shaving soaps and accessories.

-Animated water bucket.

-NECROMANTIC/EVIL ITEMS:  The shop even caters to those with...darker...tastes. (Among the list being  bloody towels, bloody robes and wearable towels, bloody bath screens, paintings, body part soaps,     and specialty colognes.) To obtain the items you will need to gain access to the private quarters of  the shop.  You may do this by either stealing the key behind Maurie (the female shop keeper), or by   killing their Gaur, located outside next to the shop.  He seems to have ate a key recently...

The shop will play a lovely tune while you are inside. When you exit the shop, the tune will stop.  Also, certain areas have been blocked off from access. You can look, but you can't touch!  We wouldn't want you helping yourself to items...now would we?

**DOES NOT REQUIRE BLOODMOON OR TRIBUNAL.  BETTER BODIES IS RECOMMENDED.**

The shopkeepers wear Better Bodies compatible clothing.  With out Better Bodies in use, the clothing will not fit right.  

Please note, you cannot access or move the mannequins.

--------------
Compatibility
--------------

A special global has been added to the mod, ensuring compatibilty with Vampire Embrace.

As with every mod made, there may be slight conflicts with the location.  Without having any and every mod running, there is no way to ensure that this exterior will not conflict with the exterior of another mod.  If this problem ensures, you can enter the shop directly by entering in the console (opened by using the ~ key) and typing in:

coc "Provincial Bath Shoppe"


However, the music script will not play if you use this method, as the doors have to be activated entering the cell for the script to begin.


-------------
Installation
-------------

Extract the included self installing archive directly into your Morrowind folder.

After installing make sure to enable the plugin in the Morrowind Launcer/Data Files menu.

7zip is a free program needed to properly extract the files.  You may download the program here:

http://www.7-zip.org

----------------------------
Credits, Usage, and Thanks
----------------------------

-Qarl for the loofahs, mirrors, brushes (the wooden mirror and fae brush are his textures), and     perfume bottles.

-Caelum Ira for making me the pillow mesh so long ago!

-Rhedd for the head meshes (faces new textures) and male Breton Hair.  Also for the head and hairs     for Cali's mannequins.

-Ireni for the hair mesh for the Breton female. I have renamed the texture and meshes.

-Robearberbil for the peasant gown, clawfoot tub, and tub water.

-NoLiv for her amazing BB clothing meshes!  The wearable towels and bathrobes use her meshes.

-TheSlof for the lotion/oil bottles.

-TextureFreak for the book textures I modified.

-Force Recon for requesting this in the first place, and for sending me the soaps he/she     retextured.They are the morrowind ingrediant soaps included in the mod.

-Dongle for the many amazing meshes. Among them are: Cauldron, Wooden Bath Tub, Wooden Basin, Water    meshes for the basins, and the glass doors used.

-Lord Yig for the rug.

-Calishan for the armor mannequins, and her kitchen jars, which I used for the bath salt container.

-The Better Bodies team for the body meshes for Cali's armor mannequins.

-Alien Slof for the mannequin's scripts.

-Dracus Draconi for the placement script, modified by Pekka, and sent to me by Alien Slof.  I later   amended it with some valuable changes made by Galsiah.  The items will now not reset to original   rotations opon re-loading your game.

-Killgore’s Home Furnishings- Animated Water Bucket (by Killgore Killack)

-Ki Shin Ju for the stand up mirrors, oval mirror, and rectangle mirror.

-Dragan for the curtains.

-Pheobe's modder pack #3 for the frames.  I was unsure about who made what frame exactly.  So thanks   to everyone involved:  Pheobe, TextureFreak, Mighty_Joe_Young, TommyKhajiit, and The_Conjure.

-A giant thank you to all the soap companies out there!  Also a giant thank you to the original       artists of all tapestries and paintings.

-Mana User and Emmansherra for the script help for the mirrors.

-Unidentical for allowing me to use the special face I made for him for the male bath merchant's       face.

-The unidentified artist of "RoseAnn.mp3".  I am unsure of where I obtained this file, as I found it   on a second harddrive of mine that hadn't been accessed in some time. 

-Princess stomper for modifying the placement script mentioned above. Thanks to her, you can not only  move the tub, but you can bathe in it as well!

-Zeravus, Unidentical, princess_stomper, Hellbishop, AlienSlof, and Faylynn for being so amazingly     awesome, and for beta testing this project.

Meshes by Me:  Robe GNDs (Boxes), powder containers, and round soaps.
Meshes by Bethesda:  Washcloths (folded and unfolded),bath rug mesh, rectangle soaps,                      mortar and pestle, tapestries, and basin.

-------
USAGE:
-------

Feel fee to use any of these items in other projects! Permission is not needed, but I do appreciate a message letting me know...as I get tickled pink when I see any of my projects in use in other projects!  Please, make sure you give the appropriate creators credit as well...and give me credit for anything of mine you used.

Always keep in mind that some of these models by be updated by me or by the other original creators at any time.  When possible, please try to obtain the original download links for any models used.

YOU MAY NOT DISTRIBUTE THE MUSIC INCLUDED IN THIS MOD.  I am unaware of where it came from, please understand.  Thank you!
                     

                   Email:    roxykittyd@adelphia.net

