                            *****The Meadow Fae******
					      by Korana

1.  What is this?
2.  Installation
3.  Changing your prexisting character into a Meadow Fae.
4.  Any issues?
5.  Credits and Usage
6.  Contact

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
1.  What is this?

The meadow fae are a race inspired by fairies.  They are slightly shorter then wood elves.
The race has different wings for the male and female variants of the race.  The females are
pale and petite, with delicatley placed leaves and flowers on their bodies.  The males are
brown and green with permanent underwear. The race uses the seamless better bodies meshes,
but no files are required from that mod.  Many heads and hairs are included.  Vampire
heads have been included, and you can also choose to play those heads as a non-vampire.

A class and birthsign are also included.

A shop that you are welcome to call home is also included.  The shop sells:

-A wig for vampire female characters
-Several variants on a rose arm wrap sheild
-Better Bodies dresses designed for the meadow fae
-A cape
-Several pairs of wings 
-Pants and shorts 
-A few loincloths and tops 

To find the shop, speak to Willow in Arrille's Tradehouse, Seyda Neen.  The shop is a nice 
under-hill house, with gentle music and butterflies.

The wings WILL work for other races, as long as clothing that does not replace the neck is 
used.  The wings are designed as Better Bodies compatable, and I make no gaurantees about
their functioning with clothing not designed for Better Bodies.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 

2.  Installation

 Extracting the files directly into your Morrowind directory should do the trick.
   But if not:
    
     - The meshes folder "MFae" should be placed in your 
          "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Meshes" directory
             **Make sure that the subfolder of "LE" is not forgotten**

     - The textures should be placed directly into your 
           "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Textures" directory

     -  The esp should be placed loosely in your
	   "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles" directory

     -  The icons folder "MFae" should be placed in your
           "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Icons" directory
     
     -  The MP3 should be placed in the 
          "Program Files/Bethesda Softworks/Morrowind/DataFiles/Music" directory

     -  This read me you can do what you please with.  

!!Make sure you enable the mod in the Morrowind Launcher before playing!!

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

3. Changing your prexisting character into a Meadow Fae:

Please note this may cause problems with your game...make sure you
backup your saves and SAVE YOUR GAME BEFORE YOU TRY THIS.

Open up the console by hitting the ~ key and type in "enableracemenu"
This will open up a menu to change your race, hair, face, etc. 
Changing your race MAY cause some temporary issues, however reloading most of the
time will solve them.
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
4.  Any known issues:


1. When you move side to side looking up the shading on the inner neck shows darker then it 
should be and the position that puts the neck in also pushes the inner neck through the 
outer neck (that sounds gross I know). Inner neck and Outer Neck reffer to sections of the
neck mesh used to properly equip clothing while using the better bodies mesh. 


2. This races suffers from the "custom Better Bodies race curse" involving first person hands. 
When a new game is started and you select female you will have the male hands in 1st person.
Save, exit, and reload the save game and you should have the female hands.

3. The pants clip.  There is currently not a suitable mesh for the body to make non clipping
pants

4. Clothing and wings MAY disappear when invisibility spells are cast, or when standing in
   water with the pixel shading option on.  This is due to the alpha channels.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~


5. Credits, Usage, and Thanks

~Robearberbil for the time and patience with me....but most importantly for adapting the wing
 meshes to my textures and for creating the rose arm wrap sheild!

~Neuman for the tight dress mesh

~NoLiv for the long dress mesh and tights mesh

~Erstam and Physcodog Studios for the seamless better bodies mesh.

~Lady E for the butterflies

~Better Heads for the head and hair meshes used.  I apologize for not going through and naming 
 each and everyone.  I was given permission to use any of the files in BH the way I saw fit. 
 It is too difficult with many of the files to determine who did what. 

~Spirit Wolf for the rugs she made for me many moons ago.

~Derreko for the loincloth and loincloth tops.

~Dale Stocker (Slyph) and Calishan (Dyrads) for inspiring this work.
 
~Brobdingnagian Bards for their song "Shepards Serenade".  Not only is it beautiful, but the
 groups is kind enough to allow people to use and distribute their work for non profit.

~Gorg for the cape/hood mesh that I modified

~Everyone that beta tested!


The meadow fae can be used however you like! It's nice if you ask, but not required.  Just
give a bit of credit if you use them in something released! Thanks.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

6. Contact

feel free to email me at:  Roxykittyd@adelphia.net 