=================================================================
Sexy_Black_Collar_Dress_v.1a
                  	By: Korana 
=================================================================

1. Installation
2. Description/Use
3. Credits
4. Contact and Usage

=================================================================
1. INSTALLATION
=================================================================

To install the plugin, unzip the .rar file into your Morrowind
directory.

=================================================================
2. DESCRIPTION/USE
=================================================================

This plugin adds the following to an NPC found in the Addamasartus.
(The cave near Seyda Neen).  She'll sell you the items, so don't kill her!

*A long black dress.  The dress is cut with high slits up the legs on 
both sides, and has deep "v" opening from the neck to the belly button.
The dress has a leather buckeled collar, long sleeves, and a semi
transparent "v" down the back.

*A double sided cloak.  The cloak is black on one side, and red on the
other.

*A pair of buckled leather plateau boots by Durgoth and Qarl that inspired
the dress.  


BETTER BODIES IS NEEDED.

SCREENSHOTs INCLUDED


This version is 1a because it's not really finished yet.  I'm releasing it per request.  However, there are a few issues I would like to address and hope to fix when real life gives me more time. 

-The dress is not perfect around the collar.  There is some misalingment where the
textures meet.  In certain positions the mesh clips in the armpit area a bit, although there is nothing I can currently do about that.

-The cape clips with itself, and it's not physiqued, so in certain positions it can clip through the player's body.  It also is not compatible with Bethesda clothing, as you will have no neck.  If this bothers you- don't use it.  I just added it for fun!

=================================================================
3. CREDITS 
=================================================================

~NoLiv for the dress mesh.

~Durgoth for the boots mesh and Qarl for the texture.

~Gorg for the original cape mesh.  I have modified it considerably.

~Thaedyn_Vyr for the vampire face mesh and original texture.  I have
 modified it considerably.  

~Gorg for the hair.


=================================================================
4. Contact & Usage
=================================================================

Please ask before using these items in a project you would like to release. 
The reason I ask is that the cape and dress are not 100% finished.  The boots
are just borrowed, and are released seperately in Durgoth's Thigh High Boots 2.0.
Please download those files for the most recent files, and for usage requirements.
The hair is part of the beauty pack, and is also borrowed.

IF you would like to contact me, please feel free.  I can be reached at:

roxykittyd@adelphia.net
