=================================================================
               Better Bodies Venom Rose Equipment
                  	By: Korana 
=================================================================

1. Installation
2. Description/Use
3. Credits
4. Contact and Usage

=================================================================
1. INSTALLATION
=================================================================

To install the plugin, unzip the .rar file into your Morrowind directory.

=================================================================
2. DESCRIPTION/USE
=================================================================

This plugin adds a new "revealing" outfit to the world of Morrowind.

The outfit consists of:

-A body suit
-Thigh High Boots
-A long cape

I have also included two weapons made by Robearberbil for other
mods of mine.  I thought they went well with the outfit, and I have
had requests to include them in other projects.

The oufits come in armor and clothing versions, you can tell which you 
are buying by name.

To buy the equipment, speak to Venom Rose.  She can be found in the 
Ald Ruhn Morag Tong guildhouse.

Better Bodies 2.0 or higher is recommended for the clothing to fit 
correctly.

Please note, the outfits may disappear under water or when using a
chameleon spell.  The cape will clip in certain positions.

=================================================================
3. CREDITS 
=================================================================

~NoLiv for the female bodysuit mesh, the boot mesh, and the GND meshes
 for both

~Rhedd for Venom Rose's head mesh

~Gorg for the cape mesh

~Siliria for the hair mesh and original texture.  I have retextured 
 it to a brighter red for this project.

~Robearberbil for the two swords

~Palinurus for giving me the motivation to finally finish the outfit

=================================================================
4. Contact & Usage
=================================================================

You may use the clothing, or the face and hair, how you wish. 
Please give credit to theabove makers for their meshes however. Please contact
Robearberbil of myself if you would like to use the weapons. I would enjoy a mention in thereadme, or maybe even an email, but it's not required!

IF you would like to contact me, please feel free.  I can be reached at:

roxykittyd@adelphia.net


Distribution- Feel free to distribute this where you like, and how you like.
AS LONG AS IT IS NOT OUTSIDE THE ELDERSCROLLS SERIES.  Thanks!